

PHD STUDENT · SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Purdue University ME3171, 610 Purdue Mall, West Lafayette, IN, 47907

 \square (415)203-8543 | \square chi45@purdue.edu | \blacktriangleleft hyung-gun.me | \square stnoah1 | \square hyung-gun | \bowtie Hyung-gun Chi

Research Interests

My research interests lie at the intersection of Computer Vision and Robotics, focusing on 3D Geometric Deep Learning for recognizing and synthesizing 3D objects. In this area, I applied Machine Learning (Deep Learning) algorithms for Augmented / Virtual Reality and Smart Factory.

Education

Purdue University

West Lafayette, IN, USA

PhD in Electrical and Computer Engineering

Advisor: Professor Karthik Ramani

Yonsei University

Seoul, South Korea

BS IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

Mar. 2010 - Feb. 2017

• Advisor: Professor Soo-Hong Lee

Advisor: Professor Soo-Hong Lee
2011-2013, 2-year military service

2011 2010, 2 year 1111111111 year

Skills.

Programming Python, Matlab, C/C++, SQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, PHP

Frameworks TensorFlow, PyTorch, Keras, ROS, OpenCV

Software Creo Parametric, SolidWorks, HyperWorks, GAZEBO

Publications and Patents

Conference Proceedings

- [C4][PDF] H. G. Chi, S. Kim, X. Hu, Q. Huang, and Karthik Ramani. A Large-scale Mechanical Components Benchmark for Deep Neural Networks. In proceedings of the 16th European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV), 2020, accepted.
- [C3][PDF] S. Kim, H. G. Chi, and Karthik Ramani. First-Person View Hand Segmentation of Multi-Modal Hand Activity Video Dataset. In proceedings of the 31st British Machine Vision Conference (BMVC), 2020, accepted.
- [C2][PDF] H. Hwang, H. G. Chi, S. H. Lee. A Research about 3D Design Data Classification with 3D Convolutional Neural Network. In *Proceedings of the Korean Computational Design and Engineering Conference*, pp. 441-442, 2017
- [C1][PDF] M. H. Woo, S. H. Kim, H. G. Chi, M. W. Park, J. K. Kim and S. H. Lee. Development of Web-based, Module Structure Platform for Surgical Workflow Management. In *Proceedings of the Korean Computational Design and Engineering Conference*, pp. 439-441, 2016

Journal Papers

- [J3][PDF] S. Kim, H. G. Chi and Karthik Ramani. Object synthesis by learning part geometry with surface and volumetric representations. In Computer-Aided Design, under review.
- [J2][PDF] S. Kim, N. Winovich, H. G. Chi, G. Lin, and K. Ramani. Latent transformations neural network for object view synthesis. In *The Visual Computer*, pp. 1-15, 2019
- [J1][PDF] H. T. Hwang, H. G. Chi, N. K. Kang, H. B. Kong and Soo-Hong Lee. An Evaluation Methodology for 3D Deep Neural Network using Visualization in 3D Data Classification. In *Journal of Mechanical Science and Technology (JMST)*, 33(3), pp. 1333-1339, 2019

Patents

• [P1][PDF] H. G. Chi. Computer Input Automation System. KR Patent (2017): 10-1745330.

Working Experience _____

Software Engineer and CEO

Seoul, South Korea

Aug. 2018 - PRESENT

NEIL LAB CORPORATION

Sep. 2016 - Dec. 2017

- Developed an office automation system using Python specifically for automating tasks such as sending an e-mail or issuing receipts, and designed a back-end system and database for customer web-service which automatically scrap and integrate customer's financial and personal data. (*Relevant patent:* [P1])
- Founded and led a startup company as a CEO for a year and also worked as a Python developer. The company was funded \$ 30,000 by the SeongNam Industry Promotion Agency.

Mechanic and Squad leader

Inje, South Korea

REPUBLIC OF KOREA ARMY

Apr. 2011 – Jan. 2013

- Maintained military weapons and equipment including firearms and vehicles.
- Led a squad as a squad leader; honored as a distinguished soldier.